If I'd known it would end up like this…
Sonumun böyle olacağını bilsem…
I never would've taken the job.
…bu işi hiç almazdım.
I didn't like it from the start.
En başından beri sevmiyordum.
It will be okay. Just take it easy.
İyileşeceksin, sakin ol.
It's not that bad. We'll be at the hospital soon.
O kadar kötü değil. Hastaneye birazdan varacağız.
I told you, no hospitals.
Hastane olmaz, dedim.
Get me to the doctor, not the hospital.
Bana doktor bul, hastane değil.
He's at Hellblau Hotel.
Hellblau Otel'de.
Look, I know what you're thinking.
Aklından ne geçtiğini biliyorum.
If you go to the hospital, the cops will come and you'll go to prison again.
Hastaneye gidersen polisler gelir, tekrar hapsi boylarsın
But we ain't got time to take you to that underground doc!
ama seni o yeraltı doktoruna götürecek vaktimiz yok!
Hellblau… Hotel!
-Hellblau Otel. -Canın hapse düşmekten daha önemli. Eğer…
Take me there now! Hellblau Hotel!
Beni oraya götür! Hellblau Otel'e!
I told you. There's always trouble when a woman's involved.
Sana demiştim, işin içine kadın karışırsa hep bir sorun çıkar.
I'm begging you… Get me to Dr. Tenma fast.
Sana yalvarıyorum. Çabuk ol. Beni Dr. Tenma'ya götür.
Make sure you're not rude.
Sakın saygısızlık etme.
The man you're about to meet
Görüşeceğin adam
isn't a person someone like you can normally meet.
senin gibi birinin normalde görüşebileceği biri değil.
I should've brought my autograph book for him to sign.
Keşke imza defterimi getirip imzasını alsaydım.
Screw around and I'll kill you.
Kafa bulursan seni gebertirim.
Come in.
Gel.
This is my man, Martin.
Adamım Martin.
You can leave now.
Sen çıkabilirsin.
What?
Efendim?
I want to speak with him privately.
Onunla baş başa konuşmak istiyorum.
All right.
Peki.
If you screw things up, I really will kill you.
İşleri batırırsan seni gerçekten gebertirim.
Can I sit here?
Buraya oturabilir miyim?
Go ahead.
Otur.
How many years have you been working for The Baby?
Kaç senedir Bebek için çalışıyorsun?
I guess it's been three years now.
Sanırım üç sene oldu.
And before that?
Peki ondan önce?
Prison, huh? How many years?
Hapishane demek. Kaç sene?
Eight years.
Sekiz yıl.
-For murder? -Yes.
-Cinayetten mi? -Evet.
You got out pretty quick for murder.
Cinayet için kısa sürede çıkmışsın.
I was a model inmate.
Örnek bir mahkûmdum.
I hear you're a model employee too.
Örnek bir çalışanmışsın da.
I'll do anything, whatever the job is. However…
Ne olursa ne iş olursa yaparım ama…
"However"?
Ama?
I don't like jobs that involve women.
Kadınların bulunduğu işleri sevmem.
I see.
Anlıyorum.
I won't say no to work.
İşi reddetmem
But I just don't like getting involved with women.
ama kadınlara bulaşmayı sevmiyorum.
This involves a woman.
Bu işte bir kadın var.
I want you to look after a certain woman for a while.
Bir süre bir kadına bakmanı istiyorum.
What a lousy job.
Ne iğrenç bir iş.
I want you to go to Düsseldorf and bring a certain woman here.
Düsseldorf'a gidip bir kadını getirmeni istiyorum.
Since you don't like getting involved with women,
Kadınlara bulaşmayı sevmediğin için
you're perfect for this job.
bu iş tam da sana göre.
I know you'll treat this job in a business-like fashion.
Bu işe profesyonelce yaklaşacağını biliyorum.
Eva Heinemann?
Eva Heinemann mı?
Who are you?
Sen kimsin?
Martin. But my name doesn't matter.
Martin ama adımın bir önemi yok.
I was told to bring you to Frankfurt.
Seni Frankfurt'a götürmem söylendi.
By whom?
Kim söyledi?
A man wearing glasses and a high-class suit.
Gözlüklü ve kaliteli takım giyen bir adam.
A man wearing glasses?
Gözlüklü bir adam mı? Roberto'nun adamı değil, değil mi?
I'm not sure.
Tam bilmiyorum
But he's a big shot.
ama çok güçlü birisi.
I won't force you if you don't want to.
İstemiyorsan seni zorlamam.
I'm not too thrilled about this either.
Bu işi ben de pek istemiyorum.
Someone is after me right now.
Şu an peşimde olan biri var.
Really?
Gerçekten mi?
Will you be my bodyguard?
Korumam olur musun?
Well, that is part of this job.
Bu işin bir kısmı da bu.
Wait there.
Burada bekle.
Carry this.
Şunu taşı.
Let's go. This is better than getting killed by that man.
Yürü, o adamın beni öldürmesinden daha iyidir.
What a pain in the ass.
Tam bir baş belası.
The way she swings her hips and the smell of her perfume…
Kalçalarını savuruşu, parfümünün kokusu.
It's ticking me off.
Asabımı bozuyor.
What a lousy job.
Ne iğrenç bir iş.
Why don't you talk?
Neden konuşmuyorsun?
Well, if you'd like, I can talk about something.
İstersen bir şeyden bahsedebilirim.
I don't want to talk.
Konuşmak istemiyorum.
Then let's not talk.
O zaman konuşmayalım.
Any liquor?
İçkin var mı?
Don't you have any liquor?
Yanında hiç içki yok mu?
Sorry, but I don't drink.
Kusura bakma, içmem.
I'll check out the dining car.
Kafeterya vagonuna bakayım.
Is that right? You're traveling on your own.
Öyle mi? Yalnız başına mı seyahat ediyorsun?
I happen to be traveling alone too.
Şansa bak, ben de yalnız seyahat ediyorum.
Say, why don't you tell me where you'll be staying?
Nerede kalacağını söylesene.
Here's my business--
Kartvizitimi vereyim…
The hell are you doing?
Ne bok yiyorsun lan?
Me? She asked me for a drink.
Ben mi? İçki içmek istedi.
Don't lay a hand on this woman.
Bu kadına elini sürme.
Why do you eat in silence?
-Neden çıt çıkarmadan yemek yiyorsun? -Dediğim gibi, istersen konuşabilirim.
Why don't you drink liquor?
Neden içki içmiyorsun?
My mom was a horrible alcoholic.
Annem çok kötü bir alkolikti.
But you can drink if you like.
Ama sen istersen içebilirsin.
I bet your mom had a good reason for drinking.
Eminim annenin içmek için geçerli bir nedeni vardır.
Do you think so?
Öyle mi dersin?
I sure do.
Eminim.
You see, I have a very good reason for my drinking.
Benim içmek için çok iyi bir nedenim var.
Go ahead. Please tell me. If you hate eating in silence, that is.
Hadi, anlat lütfen. Sessizlik içinde yemek istemiyorsan tabii.
It's a long story.
Uzun hikâye.
That's fine. Tell it.
Olsun, anlat.
I once had a fiancé.
Bir zamanlar nişanlım vardı.
He was a Japanese surgeon.
Japon bir cerrahtı.
He was an extremely gifted surgeon.
Son derece yetenekli bir cerrahtı.
And then…
Sonra da…
And then I tried to shoot and kill my ex-fiancé.
Sonra da eski nişanlımı vurarak öldürmeye çalıştım.
Does that surprise you?
Buna şaşırdın mı?
I tried to kill that guy!
O adamı öldürmeye çalıştım!
But you didn't shoot him.
Ama onu vurmadın.
Compared to my story, that's a lot better.
Benim hikâyeme kıyasla çok daha iyi.
What's your story?
Senin hikâyen ne?
Tell me.
Anlat.
I shot them.
Onları vurdum.
My woman, who was screwing another man in our bedroom,
Yatak odamızda başka bir adamla birlikte olan kadınımı vurdum.
and the man as well. I shot them until I ran out of bullets.
Adamı da vurdum. Üzerlerine şarjörü boşalttım.
The room was filled with the smell of her blood,
Oda ikisinin kan kokusu
the smell of his blood and, the smell of perfume.
ve kadının parfüm kokusuyla doldu.
When I came to my senses, I was standing there by myself.
Kendime geldiğimde tek başıma dikiliyordum.
You sure are an idiot.
Tam bir aptalsın.
That's for sure.
Orası kesin.
What a lousy job.
Ne iğrenç bir iş.
My employer is waiting inside this hotel.
Patronum bu otelde bekliyor.
You're a murderer, right?
Katilsin, değil mi?
Don't touch me.
Bana dokunma.
What room?
Hangi oda?
I'll take you there.
Ben götürürüm.
You're not dressed appropriately to enter this hotel.
Kıyafetlerin bu otele girmeye uygun değil. Burada bekleyebilirsin.
Room 1014.
1014. oda.
What a bitch.
Kaltak karı.
I don't know what the man in glasses wants from that woman,
Gözlüklü adamın o kadından ne istediğini bilmiyorum
but if she turns him down,
ama kadın onu reddederse
this lousy job will be over and I won't have to see that woman again.
bu iğrenç iş biter ve o kadını bir daha görmem.
What's wrong? You're looking a little pale.
Ne oldu? Betin benzin atmış.
It was an acceptable deal.
Kabul edilebilir bir anlaşmaydı.
I can use this card all I like.
Bu kartı dilediğimce kullanabilirim.
What are you waiting for? We're going.
Ne bekliyorsun? Gidiyoruz.
Going where?
Nereye gidiyoruz?
Shopping.
Alışverişe.
This is a lousy job.
Ne iğrenç bir iş.
This is the next place.
Şimdi burası var.
That's a men's clothing store.
Burası erkek giyim.
I need you to wear something proper.
Düzgün bir şey giymen lazım.
I'm fine like this.
Ben böyle iyiyim.
I don't like it.
Ben sevmiyorum.
I won't have the man I'm with dressed like a bum.
Yanımdaki adamın evsiz gibi giyinmesini kabul etmem.
I'll take this.
Bunu alayım.
And a necktie.
Bir de kravat.
Kenzo…
Kenzo…
Try these on.
Bunu dene.
A necktie, huh? This blows.
Kravat demek. İşte bu, kötü oldu.
-How is it? -Well…
-Nasıl? -Şey…
Nice. You're looking better.
Güzel, daha iyi oldun.
But fix that necktie.
Ama o kravatı düzelt.
Quit swaggering your shoulders like some mobster when you walk.
Yürürken çete üyesiymiş gibi omuzlarını kasmayı bırak.
I'm just walking normally.
Normal yürüyorum sadece.
Normal for you isn't normal.
Senin normalin normal değil.
From now on, you need to protect me.
Şu andan itibaren beni korumak zorundasın.
No matter where we go,
Gittiğimiz her yerde
I need you to act in a way that won't disgrace me.
beni utandırmayacak şekilde davranmalısın.
That's your job, right?
Senin işin bu, öyle değil mi?
That's right. That is my job.
Doğru. İşim bu.
Get your elbows off the table.
Dirseklerini masadan çek.
Use your fork with your left and your knife with your right.
Çatalı sol, bıçağı sağ elinle kullan.
Don't make noise when you eat.
Yerken ses çıkarma.
So, I guess it's true.
Doğruymuş sanırım.
What is?
Ne?
Your story.
Hikâyen.
About you being the classy daughter of a hospital director.
Hastane müdürünün klas bir kızı olduğun.
You thought I was lying?
Yalan attığımı mı düşündün?
Until I brought you to this city, you looked like just some alcoholic woman.
Seni bu şehre getirmeden önce sıradan bir alkolik kadına benziyordun.
What about now?
Peki şimdi?
You're a classy woman.
Klas bir kadınsın.
This is my true form.
Aslında böyle biriyim.
Eva Heinemann has returned to where she belongs.
Eva Heinemann ait olduğu yere döndü.
What's that?
O ne?
A party invitation.
Parti daveti.
-A party? -That's right.
-Parti mi? -Doğru.
This is the job I was given.
Bana verilen iş bu.
A job?
İş mi?
I'm supposed to attend several parties.
Birkaç partiye katılmam gerekiyor.
That's all.
Hepsi bu.
You must be glad. That sounds like a fun job.
Sevinmişsindir. Eğlenceli bir işe benziyor.
You're coming with me.
Sen de geliyorsun.
You'll play the part of a man who's worthy of escorting me.
Bana eşlik etmeye layık bir adam gibi davranacaksın.
This job's just getting lousier.
Bu iş daha da iğrençleşiyor.
How does it feel finally being back on your home turf?
Sonunda kendi sahana dönmek nasıl bir his?
What could be so damn funny?
Bu kadar komik olan ne acaba?
What the hell do these people here talk about anyway?
Buradaki insanlar ne konuşuyor acaba?
About the weather? What about stocks?
Hava durumunu mu? Hisseleri mi?
I don't even know what language they're speaking.
Hangi dilde konuştuklarını bile bilmiyorum.
This is making me nauseous.
Gerilmeye başladım.
So, there you are.
Buradasın demek.
Never mind me. You have fun.
Beni boş ver. Sen eğlenmeye bak.
-We're going. -Huh?
-Gidiyoruz. -Ne?
We're leaving.
Gidiyoruz dedim.
Hold on!
Şey, bir saniye.
He wasn't at this party.
Bu partide yoktu.
My job is done.
İşim tamam.
Who's not here?
Kim yoktu?
Take me away.
Götür beni.
Take me anywhere. Just get me out of here fast!
Nereye olursa. Beni hemen götür buradan!
Her hand was trembling…
Eli titriyordu…
but I didn't know why at the time.
…ama bu kez sebebini bilmiyordum.
I survived the day.
Günü atlattım.
What's the matter?
Sorun ne?
I thought you'd returned to where you belong.
Ait olduğun yere döndüğünü sanmıştım.
I used to live that kind of life every day.
Eskiden her gün öyle bir hayat yaşardım.
I thought if I returned to that world that my true self would return.
O dünyaya dönersem asıl hâlimin de geri döneceğini düşündüm.
But now, a bar like this is the only place you feel at home, huh?
Ama artık böyle bir barda kendi evinde hissediyorsun demek.
This isn't where I belong either!
Buraya da ait hissetmiyorum!
Not here! Not there either!
Buraya değil! Buraya da değil!
There is no place where I belong! I already knew that!
Ait olduğum hiçbir yer yok! Bunu zaten biliyordum!
You know, when this job is over, I'm sure I'll be murdered.
Bu iş bittiğinde öldürüleceğime eminim.
I thought it would be better than being killed by Roberto in Düsseldorf
Darmadağınık hâlde olduğum Düsseldorf'ta
I thought it would be better to be killed as the beautiful Eva Heinemann.
Güzel Eva Heinemann olarak öldürülmek daha iyi olur diye düşünmüştüm.
But when you die…
Ama ucunda ölüm varsa
it's all the same.
hepsi aynı.
I wanted to protect her.
Onu korumak istemiştim.
That's a bad habit of mine.
Kötü huyum da bu.
Out of the blue, I suddenly wanted to protect this woman.
Birdenbire bu kadını korumak istedim.
Christ! How the hell did this happen anyway?
Tanrım, böyle bir şey nasıl oldu?
That's why… we're going to Dr. Tenma… so I can tell him.
Bu yüzden Dr. Tenma'ya gidiyoruz. Ona anlatmam için.
Hang in there! Just a little longer! We're almost there!
Dayan. Az kaldı. Neredeyse geldik.
A necktie…
Kravat.
If it hadn't been for this…
Bu olmasaydı
I never would've been there.
asla orada olamazdım.
I never would've seen…
Öyle bir dehşeti
such terror.
asla görmezdim.
Subtitle translation by: Brian Athey
Alt yazı çevirmeni: Ömür Gencer